{
    "id": "Politica_252",
    "claim": "That morning I arrived a little late to'Rio Frio'and Don Sabino was already there, at the usual table where we sat on Saturdays and overlooking the Plaza de Colon. He had a coffee in front of him, a glass of water, and he looked at the newspapers of the day. As soon as I greeted us I sat down and almost without any more words pulled some folded leaflets out of the inside pocket of his jacket and said to me: 'Here, this is one of the'Memorials 'that I am writing. I wrote it last night almost at once. I want you to read it here and now and give me your opinion.\". I took those leaflets and started reading with real interest. I reproduce here the notes that I took to flyplum right there and when he authorized it, because he did not want to leave them to me or to take photocopies. The leaflets were written in his fist and handwriting. And I'll always remember his beautiful handwriting. Rest in peace, Sabino. Memories of Sabino Fernández Campo: What really happened on 23F'That afternoon, on the afternoon of February 23, 1981, I was in my office reviewing papers, like almost every afternoon, when suddenly it broke in without even knocking at the door, Fernando Gutierrez and almost shouting told me:- Sabino, fast, connect the radio!I immediately connected the radio and we both listened with amazement what all Spaniards: the screams of Tejero and the shots. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. And I felt like a whip in my whole body. I should have gone white in seconds, and without thinking about it, I jumped and went straight to the King's office. When I came in, I didn't knock at the door either, I saw that the King and Queen were already stuck to the radio and listening attentively. That's right, relax. - Sir, what's going on in Congress? - Sabino, please don't get upset. You look pale! - Sir, if there have been shots!. - I know, I heard it too. - Your Majesty, this is very serious. There may be dead!- Easy, man, easy. Don't lose your calm in difficult situations. Get in quick contact with Security and find out what's going on. - Sir, just in case I'm going to give instructions to strengthen the security of the Palace. - Yeah, I'm fine with that. The Queen had said nothing, though her face was a poem. But when I went out the phone rang and the King, while he was picking it up, asked me to wait. Then His Majesty, already on the phone, said very upset: - Alfonso!, what is it?What have these shots been?-. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - Of course I didn't hear the words on the other side of the phone or find out except from the King's answers. I want to know urgently what's going on right now there. - No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no., no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - Yeah, find out everything and you're coming to the Zarzuela.. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. At that moment and with signs I let the King know that he would postpone his answer. Then His Majesty said:- Alfonso, leave me a few minutes and call me later (and hung up the phone). - What's the matter, Sabino? - Sir, I don't know what's going on, but I think the Armed General should stay in his post. - Sir, in the midst of battle a chief cannot abandon his post. It would be nonsense. - But I just need to know what happened. The shots were not planned. - Sir, I don't understand. - Yes, Sabino, forgive me (and the King returned to his usual control). I'll explain later. Well, maybe you're right. I'll tell you now to stay at your post.'Sabino is right,'said the Queen. And then, not even three minutes had passed, the phone rang again and again it was General Armada. - Look, Alfonso, we've decided you're still there and don't move until further notice. - No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no., no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - Yes, I know, Alfonso, I know the situation is difficult and complicated. But, I insist, stay there, later we'll talk again.'Sir, I'm going to my office,'I said, amazed as I was. I'm going to gather information and give instructions to Security. - Okay, all right. And I went back to my office, where I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez. - Fernando, you have to urgently call the television, the radios and the newspapers, to find out what's going on and that News has them. Come on, quick. When I stayed I only realized that my head was a volcano and a hundred questions came up like sparkles. What was the meaning of 'it was not foreseen '?Why did the King appear to be calm with me and not with the Navy?What was that? Was it the individual action of the mad Tejero?Was it a coup d'etat?Was the bridge head of something else much more serious?. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. And doubts flooded my head! God, the situation barely let me think!. So I picked up the phone and called the special phone I had from Congress to talk to the CASA person we had highlighted that afternoon for direct information. I asked, when someone took him to the other side, for the trusted man who had stood out there because he wasn't. But the person who took it advanced me, very nervous, what had happened and what was happening, and one thing gave me such an impact that I almost fell. That Tejero had said that he did it in the name of the King!!. That clouded me to my sight and even my heart began to beat dangerously. On behalf of the King?What's going on here?Then I also called my friend Lacaci, the Captain General of Madrid, and found that he was as disoriented and disconcerted as I was. The man was trying to know exactly what was going on at the Brunete. We were left to talk and be in permanent contact, because it was essential to know what the Armoured One was going to do. And again I went to see the King. I entered the office and His Majesty was speaking on the phone and his interlocutor, who was none other than the Armed General, told him:- Alfonso, if it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King, it must be denied urgently and I want to know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing. - And just hung up the phone. I approached and without sitting, standing (there sitting the Queen followed). - Sir, I see you already know. That's very serious. - Yes, Sabino, the thing is serious. I think we should authorize the Navy to come to the Zarzuela and explain in detail what's going on, because I think things are happening here that weren't planned. - Things that were not foreseen?What does Your Majesty mean?- Well, it is a saying (but, for the first time I noticed a certain nervousness in the King, as if he wanted to hide something from me)- Well, sir, I still think that the Armed General should stay in his post. Sir, I think it's urgent that Your Majesty speak directly to the Captains General to know what they think and what's going on in their respective regions. I also think it's urgent that His Majesty publicly disprove what Tejero is saying in Congress. I think it should be addressed to the Spanish on Spanish Television. - All right, you make the arrangements with TV and as soon as you're done you come here and talk to the Captains General. So I went back to my office, where Fernando Gutierrez was supernervous, who without wasting time told me:- Sabino, the military have taken Spanish Television and National Radio. - What do you say? - I've just been confirmed by the Director General himself. At the time the phone rang. It was General Juste asking to talk to me. I quickly got in touch. - Juste, what's going on? - Sabino (General Juste and I were very close since my stay at the Army Ministry). Is the Armed General in the Zarzuela?- No, why do you ask me?- Because I have been told that at this time the Armed General had to be in the Zarzuela. - And why is that?Who has informed you of it?- Commander Pardo Zancada, who apparently knows from the mouth of General Milans. - Well, Juste, Navy isn't in the Zarzuela, neither is it nor is it expected. - Thank you, Sabino, that changes things. Thanks again. I'll call you later. - Hey, hey, why do things change?What things?- Sabino, please, I'll call you later. I hung up the phone and my head was a boil. For the first time I sensed something about the Armed General, perhaps because of his insistence on going to the Zarzuela. My instinct has already put me on guard. Also that the news of the Navy would have arrived through Milans del Bosch. And so, already with 'all the flies behind my ear ', I went back to His Majesty's office and when I entered I took the surprise of the night, what I say, the surprise of my life. Because there he was toasting. And that clouded my mind and enraged me. So, and without protocols, I turned to His Majesty and without thinking, I said to him, looking straight at him: - Sir!. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Are you crazy?We're on the edge of the cliff and you're toasting with champagne – and I almost screamed – Sir!Don't you realize that the Monarchy is in danger?Don't you realize that it can be the end of your Reign?Remember what happened to your grandfather!!!Then the King's face changed color and I saw how his hands began to tremble and in an almost inaudible voice he sent out to those present, who immediately left the office. (*) All but the Queen, who had a poker face. Once alone His Majesty came to me, and trembling and almost crying, he took me by the hands and in a supplicant tone he said to me: - Sabino, please save me! Save me, save the Monarchy, right now I do not know what I do or what to say! - Majesty, let us all calm down. This is not the time for sorrows. You yourself told me before that we should not lose our calm in difficult times. What needs to be done is to try to control the situation and to do this it is essential to talk to the Captains General. I warn you that Brunete has already taken Spanish Television and National Radio. I knew it, I knew it! - What did you know, Lord?- What was going to happenAt that moment the Queen got up and without saying anything left the office. And I collapsed. My legs were shaking. Then the King sat at his table and laid his head in his hands. I sat across the street and waited a few seconds before talking. - Sir, I don't know what Your Majesty knew, but whatever it is, now what you have to do is stop this madness. If it succeeds, the Monarchy will fall like his grandfather's. - Yeah, yeah, you're right. Please talk to the Captains General and do what you can. - No, sir, with the Captains General, the Supreme Chief of the Armed Forces has to speak, and that honor belongs to His Majesty. - Yeah, you're right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. But don't get out of here. And there I remained while the King spoke by this order, with Jaime Milans del Bosch (III Military Region), Guillermo Quintana Lacacci (I Region), Pedro Merry Gordon (II Region), Antonio Pascual Galmes (IV Region), Antonio Elícegui Prieto (V Region), Luis Polanco Mejorada (VI Region), Angel Capano Lopez (VII Region), Manuel Fernández Posse (VIII Region), Antonio Delgado Álvarez (IX Region), Manuel de la Torre Pascual (Baleares), Jesús González de Yerro (Canarias) and Ignacio Alfaro Arregui, at that time Chairman of the Board of Chiefs of Staff (JUJEM) and Luis Arebalo Peyuz, admiral head of the General Staff of the Navy. What the King talked about with the senior army commanders I will talk about in the next installment'. - This is a bomb, Sabino! - I know. - This changes everything. - I know. - This changes history. - I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. But it's the truth. - Do you know what can happen if this is published?- It will not be published, at least as long as I live. - Will your 'Memories 'be? - No, you know I'm not in favor of 'Memories'. Memories are a very serious and very detailed thing. I prefer to call this that I write'Memorials\". A'remembrance'only forces you to write what you remember. - But, I understand this is just the beginning of what happened that evening-night. - That's right, next Saturday I'll show you what I write these days, if I feel like it, because I have my doubts. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sometimes I think that the history that has been written of'that 'is already immovable. Besides, I'm looking like the Prometheus in chains. - Yeah, I'm chained to my own words and everything I've been saying since 1981. I helped create the version that has passed to history and now I'm sure they'd all face it. Because you may well think that if I lied then, now I may also be doing. Many would blame me for speaking now with resentment, for the'kick in the ass'that His Majesty gave me last year. - No, Sabino, your prestige as a serious man is beyond doubt and I'm sure they'll believe you at their feet. Many events in history have suffered significant changes and changes over time. What I'm concerned about is the position the Monarch can take if your version of now becomes public. - Well, you can imagine. - It could be until the fall of the Monarchy. - I don't think so. Although many do not believe it Spain has no other way out right now than the Monarchy. In that maybe Franco was right and everything was tied and well tied!- Yes, but the image of the King'savior of democracy 'will be over. - Well, that's true, but between History, Monarchy, King or Truth, I prefer to keep the Truth. It's my conscience. I'm going to turn 77, and I'm already, as Baroja said, on the last bend of the road. Besides, I owe it to my Lieutenant Rubio, you know the story. And that's where we left the conversation that day. That's when he told me to take the notes I wanted, knowingly, as I had shown him on many occasions that I was a tomb. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.mediterraneodigital.com",
    "date": "23/02/2018",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "I morning I he a little late I Frio'and the Director General himself my Many I Sir the trusted man who had stood out there because he wasn't I the trusted man who had stood out there because he wasn't This he I he I overlooking This I de His Majesty .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the director general who stood out there because he wasn't?",
                    "answer": "Sir"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the person who stood out because he wasn't the trusted man who stood out because he wasn't?",
                    "answer": "he I overlooking This I de His Majesty"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between I Frio and the Director General General?",
                    "score": 0.5101,
                    "answers": "I he a little late I Frio'and the Director General himself my Many I Sir the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't|appos\tthe Director General himself my Many I Sir the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't|appos\thad|aux\thad|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the trusted man who stood out there?",
                    "score": 0.4655,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I morning I he a little late I Frio'and the Director General himself my Many I Sir the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't I the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't This he I he I overlooking This I de His Majesty|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nmod\tthat I morning I he a little late I Frio'and the Director General himself my Many I Sir the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't I the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't This he I he I overlooking This I de His Majesty|npadvmod\the|dep\ta|det\ta little|amod\the a little late|amod\tI|nmod\tthe|det\thimself|appos\tmy|nmod\tMany|dep\tI|nmod\tmy Many I Sir|appos\tthe|det\ttrusted|amod\tthe trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't|appos\twho|nsubj\twho had stood out there because he was n't|relcl\tout|advmod\tout there|advmod\tbecause|mark\the|nsubj\tbecause he was n't|advcl\tn't|neg\tI the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't This he I he I overlooking This I de His Majesty|appos\tthe|det\ttrusted|amod\tthe trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't This he I he I overlooking This I de His Majesty|appos\twho|nsubj\twho had stood out there because he was n't This he I he I overlooking This I de His Majesty|relcl\tout|advmod\tout there|advmod\tbecause|mark\the|nsubj\tbecause he was n't This he I he I overlooking This I de His Majesty|advcl\tn't|neg\tThis he I he I overlooking|dep\the|appos\tI|meta\the|meta\tI|meta\toverlooking|meta\tThis|dep\tI|dep\tde|dep\tHis|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.4157,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "His Majesty my office,'I I This the King he Don Sabino I the King General Juste he General Juste I the King I the King's I day.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that His Majesty my office said, 'I I This the King he Don Sabino I the King General Juste he General Juste he General Juste I the King'?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of His Majesty's office?",
                    "answer": "This the King"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the person who was in charge of His Majesty's office on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "Don Sabino"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of His Majesty's office?",
                    "answer": "General Juste I the King"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the King General Juste I the King?",
                    "score": 0.6021,
                    "answers": "I This the King he Don Sabino I the King|nmod\tThis the King|appos\tI the King|appos\tI the King|nmod\tI the King|nmod\t's|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the head of the King's office?",
                    "score": 0.5896,
                    "answers": "that His Majesty my office,'I I This the King he Don Sabino I the King General Juste he General Juste I the King I the King 's I day|dobj\tmy|poss\tmy office,'I|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the King and Don Sabino I the King?",
                    "score": 0.5881,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tHis|poss\tThis|det\tthe|det\the|nmod\tthe|det\the|nmod\tthe|det\tthe|det\tI|nmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.4942,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I Many as I Tejero you Many the Armed General you the Armed General this you the Zarzuela?- he you my office,'I the Monarchy my office,'I I the Queen you jacket the Armed General the television, the radios and the newspapers the King His Majesty you the television, the radios and the newspapers shots he .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I Many as I Tejero you Many the Armed General?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "this you the Zarzuela?-"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "Monarchy"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "Monarchy"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.473,
                    "answers": "I the Queen you jacket the Armed General the television , the radios and the newspapers|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the head of the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.4687,
                    "answers": "Many the Armed General|nmod\tthe Armed General|appos\tyou the Armed General this|dep\tthe Armed General|appos\tI the Queen you jacket|nmod\tthe Armed General|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.3913,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "my friend Lacaci, the Captain General of Madrid you the Queen he my friend Lacaci, the Captain General of Madrid this madness .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is Lacaci?",
                    "answer": "the Captain General of Madrid"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captain General of Madrid?",
                    "score": 0.6821,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid you the Queen he my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid this madness|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tLacaci ,|appos\t,|punct\tthe|det\tCaptain|compound\tthe Captain General of Madrid|appos\tof Madrid|prep\tthe|det\the|dep\tyou the Queen he my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid|appos\t,|punct\tthe|det\tCaptain|compound\tthe Captain General of Madrid|appos\tof Madrid|prep\tthis|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Lacaci and Lacaci?",
                    "score": 0.6497,
                    "answers": "my|poss\tthat my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid you the Queen he my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid this madness|dobj\tmy|poss\the my friend|dep\tthis madness|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5891,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "this madness my friend Lacaci, the Captain General of Madrid this madness to read he I and the Monarchy Don Sabino I .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the madness?",
                    "answer": "to read he I and the Monarchy"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Monarchy of Madrid?",
                    "answer": "Don Sabino"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Lacaci say about Don Sabino I?",
                    "score": 0.7311,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Captain General of Madrid in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.6519,
                    "answers": "Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid|appos\tthe Captain General of Madrid|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of Lacaci's friend who read he I and the Monarchy Don Sabino I?",
                    "score": 0.6441,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that this madness my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid this madness to read he I and the Monarchy Don Sabino I|ROOT\tthat this madness my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid this madness to read he I and the Monarchy Don Sabino I|npadvmod\tCaptain|compound\the|dep\tSabino|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Don Sabino I and the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.6377,
                    "answers": "this madness to read he I and the Monarchy Don Sabino I|appos\tDon|compound\tDon Sabino I|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Lacaci's thoughts on Don Sabino I?",
                    "score": 0.6188,
                    "answers": "my|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the Armed General General Juste the Armed General my friend Lacaci, the Captain General of Madrid the Zarzuela?- the Queen with the Captains General .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Captain General of Madrid the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "the Queen"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captain General of Madrid the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.5828,
                    "answers": "the Captain General of Madrid the Zarzuela?- the Queen with the Captains General|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captains General of Madrid?",
                    "score": 0.573,
                    "answers": "with the Captains General|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the armed general Juste the Armed General and the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.5632,
                    "answers": "that the Armed General General Juste the Armed General my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid the Zarzuela?- the Queen with the Captains General|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.442,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the Captains General the Monarchy that I I the Captains General the Captains General when Don Sabino he it, because Don Sabino did the Captains General want his post His Majesty you take you .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did the Captains General want his post His Majesty you take?",
                    "answer": "Don Sabino"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why did the Captains General want his post His Majesty you take you?",
                    "answer": "because Don Sabino did the Captains General want his post His Majesty you take you"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did the Captains General want his post?",
                    "score": 0.8389,
                    "answers": ", because Don Sabino did the Captains General want his post His Majesty you take you|parataxis"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What position did Don Sabino hold during his time as Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.8005,
                    "answers": "the|det\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Don Sabino do to the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.7678,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that the Captains General the Monarchy that I I the Captains General the Captains General when Don Sabino he it , because Don Sabino did the Captains General want his post His Majesty you take you|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Captains General before Don Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.6994,
                    "answers": "I the Captains General|appos\tthe Captains General|appos\tthe Captains General|appos\tthe Captains General|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5489,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the Queen I written in my .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that the Queen I wrote in my journal was the Queen?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the first Queen to write in a journal?",
                    "score": 0.8092,
                    "answers": "the|det\tI|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Queen write in her journal in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7573,
                    "answers": "that the Queen I written in my|ccomp\tI written in my|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Queen of Ireland in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7251,
                    "answers": "in my|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that the Queen I wrote in?",
                    "score": 0.6676,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5757,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the Monarchy he 'll always the phone the Monarchy the Truth .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who 'll always the phone the Monarchy the Truth?",
                    "answer": "he"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the Monarchy the Truth?",
                    "score": 0.7644,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that the Monarchy he 'll always the phone the Monarchy the Truth|ROOT\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthe Monarchy|dep\t'll always|acl\talways|advmod\tthe|det\tthe|det\t'll always the phone the Monarchy|dep\tthe|det\tthat the Monarchy he 'll always the phone the Monarchy the Truth|parataxis"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6533,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I the Armed General Spanish Television .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I was the Armed General Spanish Television?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the armed general Spanish Television?",
                    "score": 0.7073,
                    "answers": "Armed|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of I the Armed General Spanish Television?",
                    "score": 0.6672,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I the Armed General Spanish Television|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.6094,
                    "answers": "the Armed General|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5293,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tSpanish|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5188,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Spanish Television the Armed General he I the situation : the Zarzuela?- Spanish Television I Tejero entered he my Lieutenant Rubio Navy you the Captains General shots the version that has passed to history every afternoon, when suddenly it my Lieutenant Rubio Tejero I you knocking I door, Fernando I Spanish Television my Lieutenant Rubio Spanish Television told me:- I , fast, connect the radio!I immediately connected the radio and we both listened with amazement what all Spaniards: the screams of Tejero and the shots.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "I the situation"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who knocked on the door of Spanish Television?",
                    "answer": "I"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who told me to connect the radio?",
                    "answer": "Fernando I Spanish Television my Lieutenant Rubio Spanish Television"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who knocked on the door of Spanish Television?",
                    "answer": "I"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Lt. Rubio Tejero do to connect the radio to the radio?",
                    "score": 0.6491,
                    "answers": "my Lieutenant Rubio Navy|appos\tto history|prep\tfast|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Lt. Gov. Marco Rubio say to Tejero?",
                    "score": 0.6389,
                    "answers": "that has passed to history every afternoon|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Lt. Gov. Rubio Tejero?",
                    "score": 0.6066,
                    "answers": "you the Captains General|nmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Tejero do with the radio?",
                    "score": 0.6032,
                    "answers": "I Tejero entered he my Lieutenant Rubio Navy you the Captains General shots the version that has passed to history every afternoon|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the exchange between Tejero and Rubio?",
                    "score": 0.59,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\the I the situation :|appos\tshots|dep\tSpanish Television my Lieutenant Rubio Spanish Television|appos\twe both listened with amazement what all Spaniards : the screams of Tejero and the shots|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And I felt like a whip in my whole body.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I felt like a whip in my whole body?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the website report that I felt like in my whole body?",
                    "answer": "a whip"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a whip and a whip?",
                    "score": 0.7239,
                    "answers": "a whip|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about his body?",
                    "score": 0.6756,
                    "answers": "in my whole body|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5763,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5447,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that And I felt like a whip in my whole body|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tAnd|cc\tI|nsubj\ta|det\tmy|poss\twhole|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5329,
                    "answers": "like a whip|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I should have gone white in seconds, and without thinking about it, I jumped and went straight to the King's office.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did I do without thinking about it?",
                    "answer": "jumped and went straight to the King's office"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to go white?",
                    "score": 0.8176,
                    "answers": "in seconds|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Dr. George Flinn say about the King's office?",
                    "score": 0.7776,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I should have gone white in seconds , and without thinking about it , I jumped and went straight to the King 's office|ROOT\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\thave|aux\twhite|acomp\t,|punct\tit|pobj\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tstraight|advmod\tthe|det\t's|case"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about the incident?",
                    "score": 0.7253,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat I should have gone white in seconds|ccomp\twithout thinking about it , I jumped and went straight to the King 's office|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of going to the King's office?",
                    "score": 0.7235,
                    "answers": "went straight to the King 's office|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where was the King's office when the incident happened?",
                    "score": 0.7231,
                    "answers": "the King 's office|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "When I came in, I didn't knock at the door either, I saw that the King and Queen were already stuck to the radio and listening attentively.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who were already stuck to the radio and listening attentively?",
                    "answer": "the King and Queen"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the King and Queen get stuck listening to the radio?",
                    "score": 0.7368,
                    "answers": "the King and Queen|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between the King and Queen?",
                    "score": 0.5731,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tWhen|advmod\tI|nsubj\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tdid|aux\tn't|neg\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tand|cc\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.4844,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.4725,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tin|advmod\tthe|det\teither|advmod\tthat|mark\tthe|det\talready|advmod\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Sir, what's going on in Congress? - Sabino, please don't get upset.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Sir, what's going on in Congress?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Sabino say?",
                    "answer": "please don't get upset"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's role in Congress?",
                    "score": 0.7315,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t-|punct\tSir|npadvmod\t,|punct\twhat|nsubj\t's|aux\tSir , what 's going on in Congress ?|advcl\ton|prt\tin Congress|prep\t?|punct\t-|punct\t,|punct\tplease|intj\tdo|aux\tthat - Sir , what 's going on in Congress ? - Sabino , please do n't get upset|ccomp\tupset|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sabino and Trump?",
                    "score": 0.7211,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "You look pale! - Sir, if there have been shots!.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that You look pale?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How did you look pale?",
                    "answer": "if there have been shots!"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of how pale you look?",
                    "score": 0.8667,
                    "answers": "You|nsubj\tpale|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.7394,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Dr. Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6889,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that You look pale ! - Sir , if there have been shots !|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Your Majesty, this is very serious.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Your Majesty, this is very serious?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.7878,
                    "answers": "Your Majesty|npadvmod\tthat - Your Majesty , this is very serious|ccomp\tvery serious|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6306,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6129,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Your Majesty , this is very serious|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tYour|poss\t,|punct\tthis|nsubj\tvery|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There may be dead!- Easy, man, easy.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the site that reported that there may be dead?",
                    "answer": "Easy, man, easy"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about death?",
                    "score": 0.7543,
                    "answers": "dead!-|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the dead man?",
                    "score": 0.6993,
                    "answers": "man|intj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5934,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5465,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\t,|punct\t,|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Don't lose your calm in difficult situations.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that don't lose your calm in difficult situations?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5689,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj\twww.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Do n't lose your calm in difficult situations|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5641,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tDo|aux\tn't|neg\tthat Do n't lose your calm in difficult situations|ccomp\tyour|poss\tyour calm|dobj\tin difficult situations|prep\tdifficult|amod\tdifficult situations|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Get in quick contact with Security and find out what's going on.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that they were in quick contact with Security?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.6589,
                    "answers": "that Get in quick contact with Security and find out what 's going on|ccomp\tquick|amod\tquick contact with Security|pobj\t's|aux\twhat 's going on|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between security and hijacking?",
                    "score": 0.6265,
                    "answers": "with Security|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of what is going on?",
                    "score": 0.5534,
                    "answers": "find out what 's going on|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5485,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5349,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Get in quick contact with Security and find out what 's going on|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tin quick contact with Security|prep\tand|cc\tout|prt\twhat|nsubj\ton|prt"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Sir, just in case I'm going to give instructions to strengthen the security of the Palace.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Sir, just in case I'm going to give instructions to strengthen the security of the Palace?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the security of the Palace?",
                    "score": 0.6885,
                    "answers": "I 'm going to give instructions to strengthen the security of the Palace|acl\tto give instructions to strengthen the security of the Palace|xcomp\tto strengthen the security of the Palace|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5902,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The Queen had said nothing, though her face was a poem.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that The Queen had said nothing?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What poem did the Queen say on 23/02/2018?",
                    "score": 0.7969,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\thad|aux\tnothing|dobj\t,|punct\tthough|mark\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the poem that the Queen wrote?",
                    "score": 0.7622,
                    "answers": "The Queen|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6601,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But when I went out the phone rang and the King, while he was picking it up, asked me to wait.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that But when I went out the phone rang and the King asked me to wait?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened to the phone when I went out?",
                    "answer": "when I went out the phone rang"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the King ask the King to do?",
                    "score": 0.7243,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that But when I went out the phone rang and the King , while he was picking it up , asked me to wait|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did the King wait for the phone to ring?",
                    "score": 0.6784,
                    "answers": "that But when I went out the phone rang and the King , while he was picking it up , asked me to wait|ccomp\tthe King , while he was picking it up , asked me to wait|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between the King and Mediterraneodigital.?",
                    "score": 0.5942,
                    "answers": "But|cc\twhen|advmod\tout|advmod\twhile|mark\the|nsubj\tup|prt\tme|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the phone that the King was picking up?",
                    "score": 0.5632,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5553,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Then His Majesty, already on the phone, said very upset: - Alfonso!, what is it?What have these shots been?-.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that His Majesty was upset?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between King Alfonso and Queen Elizabeth II?",
                    "score": 0.7397,
                    "answers": "very upset|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Alfonso and his Majesty?",
                    "score": 0.735,
                    "answers": "that Then His Majesty , already on the phone , said very upset : - Alfonso ! , what is|ccomp\tAlfonso ! , what is|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the exchange between the Queen and Alfonso?",
                    "score": 0.6745,
                    "answers": "Then|advmod\tthe|det\tit?What|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is Mediterraneodigital located?",
                    "score": 0.6564,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the phone that the Queen was on?",
                    "score": 0.5968,
                    "answers": "the phone|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Of course I didn't hear the words on the other side of the phone or find out except from the King's answers.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "- Of course I didn't hear the words on the other side of the phone or find out except from the King's answers"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the King say on the other side of the phone?",
                    "score": 0.6005,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Of course I did n't hear the words on the other side of the phone or find out except from the King 's answers|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tOf|advmod\tOf course|advmod\tdid|aux\tn't|neg\tthat - Of course I did n't hear the words on the other side of the phone or find out except from the King 's answers|ccomp\tthe words on the other side of the phone|dobj\ton the other side of the phone|prep\tother|amod\tthe other side of the phone|pobj\tthe phone|pobj\tfind out except from the King 's answers|conj\tout|prt\texcept from the King 's answers|prep\tfrom the King 's answers|prep\tthe King 's|poss\t's|case\tthe King 's answers|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the phone?",
                    "score": 0.5669,
                    "answers": "of the phone|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5379,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the date of the article?",
                    "score": 0.5528,
                    "answers": "23/02/2018|pobj\t, no , no ,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that is linked to Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5509,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - No , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5492,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5161,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat -|punct\tNo , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno , no , no , no , no , no ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t, no ,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tNo , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no|intj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Yeah, find out everything and you're coming to the Zarzuela.. I'm sorry.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Yeah, find out everything and you're coming to the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the website say about the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "I'm sorry"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is the Zarzuela located?",
                    "score": 0.8147,
                    "answers": "to the Zarzuela|prep\tthe Zarzuela|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com find out about the Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.782,
                    "answers": "that - Yeah , find out everything and you 're coming to the Zarzuela|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about the Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.7779,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tyou 're coming to the Zarzuela|conj\tsorry|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.7207,
                    "answers": "-|punct\tYeah|intj\t,|punct\tout|prt\teverything|dobj\t're|aux\tI 'm sorry|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is Mediterraneodigital.com located?",
                    "score": 0.7103,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Yeah , find out everything and you 're coming to the Zarzuela ..|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "At that moment and with signs I let the King know that he would postpone his answer.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I let the King know that he would postpone his answer?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the King announce that he would postpone his answer?",
                    "score": 0.8032,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that At that moment and with signs I let the King know that he would postpone his answer|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat moment|pobj\tand|cc\twith signs|conj\tI|nsubj\tthat At that moment and with signs I let the King know that he would postpone his answer|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe King know that he would postpone his answer|ccomp\the|nsubj\tthat he would postpone his answer|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the King say about postponement of his answer?",
                    "score": 0.7491,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat|det\tsigns|pobj\tthat|mark\twould|aux\this|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5409,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Then His Majesty said:- Alfonso, leave me a few minutes and call me later (and hung up the phone).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did His Majesty say to Alfonso?",
                    "answer": "leave me a few minutes and call me later"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Alfonso and His Majesty?",
                    "score": 0.6917,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Then His Majesty said:- Alfonso , leave me a few minutes and call me later ( and hung up the phone )|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5523,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- What's the matter, Sabino? - Sir, I don't know what's going on, but I think the Armed General should stay in his post.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - What's the matter, Sabino?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who should stay in his post?",
                    "answer": "the Armed General"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Sabino think about the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.731,
                    "answers": "I think the Armed General should stay in his post|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.6979,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's political affiliation?",
                    "score": 0.6173,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - What 's the matter , Sabino ?|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.5868,
                    "answers": "the Armed General|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's position in the armed forces?",
                    "score": 0.582,
                    "answers": "n't|neg\t's|aux\tshould|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Sir, in the midst of battle a chief cannot abandon his post.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that Sir, in the midst of battle a chief cannot abandon his post?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the story that the chief cannot abandon his post in the midst of battle?",
                    "score": 0.7739,
                    "answers": "the midst of battle|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a chief and a chief?",
                    "score": 0.7272,
                    "answers": "a chief|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6209,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5815,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t-|punct\t,|punct\tthe|det\tcan|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It would be nonsense.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that it would be nonsense?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6652,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6256,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that It would be nonsense|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tIt|nsubj\twould|aux\tthat It would be nonsense|ccomp\tnonsense|acomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The shots were not planned.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did themediterraneodigital.com report that the shots were not planned?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many shots were planned?",
                    "score": 0.8026,
                    "answers": "that The shots were not planned|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the number of shots taken?",
                    "score": 0.7572,
                    "answers": "were|auxpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.675,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.648,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThe|det\tnot|neg"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Sir, I don't understand.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Sir, I don't understand?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.794,
                    "answers": "Sir|npadvmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about the claim?",
                    "score": 0.7899,
                    "answers": "that - Sir , I do n't understand|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6487,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6329,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Sir , I do n't understand|ROOT\tthat|mark\t-|punct\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tdo|aux\tn't|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the quotes from the Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6177,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Yes, Sabino, forgive me (and the King returned to his usual control).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Sabino do to the King?",
                    "answer": "forgive me"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the King forgive Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.8326,
                    "answers": "that - Yes , Sabino , forgive me ( and the King returned to his usual control|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sabino and the King?",
                    "score": 0.6559,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Yes , Sabino , forgive me ( and the King returned to his usual control )|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tYes|intj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tme|dobj\t(|punct\tand|cc\tthe|det\tthe King|nsubj\t( and the King returned to his usual control|ccomp\tto his usual control|prep\this|poss\tusual|amod\this usual control|pobj\t)|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5488,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I'll tell you now to stay at your post.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I'll tell you to stay at your post?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about staying at a post?",
                    "score": 0.7962,
                    "answers": "that I 'll tell you now to stay at your post|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6144,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj\twww.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I 'll tell you now to stay at your post|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5752,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\t'll|aux\tyou|dobj\tnow|advmod\tto|aux\tat your post|prep\tyour|poss\tyour post|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'Sabino is right,'said the Queen.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that 'Sabino is right'?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the Queen say about Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.8308,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that ' Sabino is right,'said the Queen|ROOT\t' Sabino is right,'said|nmod\tthat ' Sabino is right,'said the Queen|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sabino and the Queen?",
                    "score": 0.6974,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t'|punct\tright,'said|acomp\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6331,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And then, not even three minutes had passed, the phone rang again and again it was General Armada.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that the phone rang again and again?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was on the phone on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "General Armada"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When was the last time the phone rang from Armada?",
                    "score": 0.7556,
                    "answers": "that And then , not even three minutes had passed , the phone rang again and again it was General Armada|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take for the phone to ring again and again?",
                    "score": 0.731,
                    "answers": "not even three minutes|nsubj\tnot even three minutes had passed|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the phone number of General Armada in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7105,
                    "answers": "the phone|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the date of the phone call from General Armada?",
                    "score": 0.6856,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the General Armada?",
                    "score": 0.6763,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tAnd|cc\tthen|advmod\t,|punct\teven|advmod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tagain|advmod\tand|cc\tagain|advmod\tit|nsubj\tagain it was General Armada|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Look, Alfonso, we've decided you're still there and don't move until further notice.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that Alfonso was still there?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to move?",
                    "score": 0.8137,
                    "answers": "you 're still there and do n't move until further notice|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Alfonso and MS-13?",
                    "score": 0.7036,
                    "answers": "that - Look , Alfonso , we 've decided you 're still there and do n't move until further notice|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5834,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the date of the article?",
                    "score": 0.5528,
                    "answers": "23/02/2018|pobj\t, no , no ,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that is linked to Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5509,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - No , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5492,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5161,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat -|punct\tNo , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno , no , no , no , no , no ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t, no ,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno ,|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\tno|intj\t,|punct\tno|intj\t,|punct\tNo , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no , no|intj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Yes, I know, Alfonso, I know the situation is difficult and complicated.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Yes, I know, Alfonso, I know the situation is difficult and complicated?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of situation is the situation?",
                    "answer": "difficult"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Alfonso and Rodrigo Duterte?",
                    "score": 0.7843,
                    "answers": "that - Yes , I know , Alfonso , I know the situation is difficult and complicated|ccomp\tthe situation is difficult and complicated|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Alfonso's knowledge of the political situation?",
                    "score": 0.7181,
                    "answers": "I|nsubj\tI|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6511,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I'm going to gather information and give instructions to Security.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I'm going to gather information and give instructions to Security?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the meeting between Trump and Vladimir Putin?",
                    "score": 0.7666,
                    "answers": "I|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of intelligence gathering?",
                    "score": 0.7438,
                    "answers": "that I 'm going to gather information and give instructions to Security|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What information did Mediterraneodigital.com gather on 23/02/2018?",
                    "score": 0.739,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5848,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And I went back to my office, where I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that And I went back to my office, where I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did I wait in distress for?",
                    "answer": "Fernando Gutierrez"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Gutierrez do to help her?",
                    "score": 0.7772,
                    "answers": "to my office , where I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the cause of distress for Fernando Gutierrez?",
                    "score": 0.7703,
                    "answers": "that And I went back to my office , where I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez|ccomp\tback to my office , where I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez|advmod\tmy office , where I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez|pobj\twhere I waited in distress for Fernando Gutierrez|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Gutierrez's distress?",
                    "score": 0.7113,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tAnd|cc\tI|nsubj\tmy|poss\t,|punct\twhere|advmod\tI|nsubj\tin distress|prep\tdistress|pobj\tfor Fernando Gutierrez|prep\tFernando|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.64,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Fernando, you have to urgently call the television, the radios and the newspapers, to find out what's going on and that News has them.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why do you have to call the television, the radios and the newspapers?",
                    "answer": "to find out what's going on"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the news in India?",
                    "score": 0.5388,
                    "answers": "the newspapers|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the method used to find out what news is going on?",
                    "score": 0.5329,
                    "answers": "that - Fernando , you have to urgently call the television , the radios and the newspapers , to find out what 's going on and that News has them|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the telephone numbers that you need to call to find out what's going on and that News has them?",
                    "score": 0.4815,
                    "answers": "to urgently call the television , the radios and the newspapers|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the news and the media?",
                    "score": 0.4799,
                    "answers": "that News has them|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.4202,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "When I stayed I only realized that my head was a volcano and a hundred questions came up like sparkles.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was my head like when I stayed at Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "answer": "a volcano"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Dr. George Flinn say about his head being a volcano?",
                    "score": 0.7144,
                    "answers": "that my head was a volcano|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many questions came up like sparkles?",
                    "score": 0.6626,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat When I stayed I only realized that my head was a volcano and a hundred questions came up like sparkles|ccomp\tmy head|nsubj\ta volcano|attr\ta hundred questions|nsubj\ta hundred questions came up like sparkles|conj\tlike sparkles|prep\tsparkles|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5387,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5168,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tWhen|advmod\tI|nsubj\tI|nsubj\tonly|advmod\tthat|mark\tmy|poss\ta|det\tand|cc\ta|quantmod\tup|prt"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "What was the meaning of 'it was not foreseen '?Why did the King appear to be calm with me and not with the Navy?What was that? Was it the individual action of the mad Tejero?Was it a coup d'etat?Was the bridge head of something else much more serious?.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the meaning of 'it was not foreseen'?",
                    "answer": "it was not foreseen"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the meaning of 'it was not foreseen'?",
                    "answer": "it was not foreseen"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the meaning of 'it was not foreseen'?",
                    "answer": "it was not foreseen"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the meaning of the coup d'etat?",
                    "score": 0.7876,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj\twww.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that What was the meaning of ' it was not foreseen ' ?|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tWhat|attr\tthat What was the meaning of ' it was not foreseen '|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe meaning of ' it was not foreseen '|nsubj\tof ' it was not foreseen '|prep\t'|punct\tit|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\tnot|neg\tit was not foreseen|pcomp\t'|punct\t?|punct\tWhy|advmod\tdid|aux\tthe|det\tthe King|nsubj\tWhy did the King appear to be calm with me and not with the Navy?What|ROOT\tto|aux\tto be calm with me and not with|xcomp\tcalm|acomp\twith me and not with|prep\tme|pobj\tand|cc\tnot|neg\tnot with|conj\tthe|det\tthe Navy?What|oprd\twas that ?|ROOT\tthat|nsubj\t?|punct\tit|nsubj\tthe|det\tindividual|amod\tof the mad Tejero?Was|prep\tthe|det\tmad|amod\tthe mad Tejero?Was|pobj\tit|nsubj\ta|det\tcoup|nmod\ta coup d'etat?Was|attr\tthe|det\tof something else much more serious|prep\tsomething else much more serious|pobj\telse|advmod\tmuch|advmod\tmuch more|advmod\tmuch more serious|amod\t?|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And doubts flooded my head! God, the situation barely let me think!.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did doubts flood my head?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the website say about the doubts that flooded my head?",
                    "answer": "God, the situation barely let me think!"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between God and the economy?",
                    "score": 0.6611,
                    "answers": "God , the situation barely let me think !|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the doubts that flooded my head?",
                    "score": 0.6345,
                    "answers": "that And doubts flooded my head|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.?",
                    "score": 0.6219,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that And doubts flooded my head !|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6216,
                    "answers": "my head|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6194,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "So I picked up the phone and called the special phone I had from Congress to talk to the CASA person we had highlighted that afternoon for direct information.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did I pick up the phone and call the special phone I had from Congress?",
                    "answer": "to talk to the CASA person we had highlighted that afternoon for direct information"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of calling a CASA person?",
                    "score": 0.5648,
                    "answers": "that So I picked up the phone and called the special phone I had from Congress to talk to the CASA person we had highlighted that afternoon for direct information|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the special phone I had from Congress to talk to CASA?",
                    "score": 0.5116,
                    "answers": "special|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.4134,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I asked, when someone took him to the other side, for the trusted man who had stood out there because he wasn't.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that someone took him to the other side?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who took the man to the other side?",
                    "score": 0.5644,
                    "answers": "when someone took him to the other side|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about the trusted man?",
                    "score": 0.5406,
                    "answers": "for the trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't|prep\tthe trusted man who had stood out there because he was n't|pobj\twho had stood out there because he was n't|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the trusted man who stood out there because he wasn't a trusted man?",
                    "score": 0.5181,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tto the other side|prep\tthe other side|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5105,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But the person who took it advanced me, very nervous, what had happened and what was happening, and one thing gave me such an impact that I almost fell.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that But the person who took it advanced me, very nervous, what had happened and what was happening?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What gave me such an impact that I almost fell?",
                    "answer": "one thing"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How did the person who took it advanced me?",
                    "score": 0.7604,
                    "answers": "that But the person who took it advanced me , very nervous , what had happened and what was happening , and one thing gave me such an impact that I almost fell|ccomp\tsuch an impact that I almost fell|dobj\tthat I almost fell|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5197,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "That Tejero had said that he did it in the name of the King!!.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who said that he did it in the name of the King?",
                    "answer": "That Tejero"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Tejero say about the King?",
                    "score": 0.7795,
                    "answers": "That Tejero|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Tejero do in the name of the King?",
                    "score": 0.77,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that That Tejero had said that he did it in the name of the King !|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tThat|det\thad|aux\tthat|mark\the|nsubj\tit|dobj\tin the name of the King|prep\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe King|pobj\t!|punct\t!|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5742,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "That clouded me to my sight and even my heart began to beat dangerously.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What part of my body began to beat dangerously?",
                    "answer": "my heart"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What clouded me to my sight?",
                    "score": 0.8003,
                    "answers": "that That clouded me to my sight and even my heart began to beat dangerously|ccomp\tto my sight|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about his heart?",
                    "score": 0.7126,
                    "answers": "even my heart began to beat dangerously|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5887,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5783,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tThat|nsubj\tme|dobj\tmy|poss\tand|cc\teven|advmod\tmy|poss\tto|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "On behalf of the King?What's going on here?Then I also called my friend Lacaci, the Captain General of Madrid, and found that he was as disoriented and disconcerted as I was.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on behalf of the King?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Captain General of Madrid in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.6073,
                    "answers": "Captain|compound\tthe Captain General of Madrid|appos\tof Madrid|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Lacaci and the King?",
                    "score": 0.5948,
                    "answers": "I also called my friend Lacaci , the Captain General of Madrid , and found that he was as disoriented and disconcerted as I was|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The man was trying to know exactly what was going on at the Brunete.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018",
                    "answer": "The man was trying to know exactly what was going on at the Brunete"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the man trying to know exactly what was going on at Brunete?",
                    "score": 0.7106,
                    "answers": "the|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5957,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We were left to talk and be in permanent contact, because it was essential to know what the Armoured One was going to do.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that we were left to talk and be in permanent contact?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why was it essential to know what the Armoured One was going to do?",
                    "score": 0.7794,
                    "answers": "essential|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Armoured One do?",
                    "score": 0.7513,
                    "answers": "because it was essential to know the Armoured One was going what to do|advcl\tthe Armoured One was going what to do|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about the Armoured One?",
                    "score": 0.6761,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that We were left to talk and be in permanent contact , because it was essential to know the Armoured One was going what to do|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tWe|nsubjpass\twere|auxpass\tto|aux\tto talk and be in permanent contact|xcomp\tand|cc\tbe in permanent contact|conj\tin permanent contact|prep\t,|punct\tbecause|mark\tit|nsubj\tto|aux\tto know the Armoured One was going what to do|xcomp\twhat|dobj\tthe|det\twas|aux\tto|aux\twhat to do|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the Armoured One?",
                    "score": 0.6624,
                    "answers": "Armoured|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Armoured One and the Armoured one?",
                    "score": 0.6214,
                    "answers": "permanent|amod\tpermanent contact|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And again I went to see the King.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I went to see the King?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did I go to see on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "the King"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did the King meet Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6769,
                    "answers": "that And again I went to see the King|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the King of Egypt in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.6715,
                    "answers": "the King|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5883,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.58,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that And again I went to see the King|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tAnd|cc\tagain|advmod\tI|nsubj\tto|aux\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the King and Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5309,
                    "answers": "to see the King|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I entered the office and His Majesty was speaking on the phone and his interlocutor, who was none other than the Armed General, told him:- Alfonso, if it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King, it must be denied urgently and I want to know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the interlocutor of the Armed General?",
                    "answer": "Tejero"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Tejero say to the King?",
                    "score": 0.6846,
                    "answers": "why Tejero said such a thing|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the King say to Tejero?",
                    "score": 0.6683,
                    "answers": "the King|pobj\turgently|advmod\tI want to know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing|conj\tto know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing|xcomp\turgently|advmod\tthe King|nsubj\talmost|advmod\t– and the King almost shouted –|parataxis\tsuch a thing|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the madman who entered the Congress?",
                    "score": 0.6132,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I entered the office and His Majesty was speaking on the phone and his interlocutor , who was none other than the Armed General , told him:- Alfonso , if it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King , it must be denied urgently and I want to know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing|ROOT\tthat I entered the office and His Majesty was speaking on the phone and his interlocutor , who was none other than the Armed General , told him:- Alfonso , if it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King , it must be denied urgently and I want to know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing|ccomp\tHis Majesty|nsubj\tHis Majesty was speaking on the phone and his interlocutor , who was none other than the Armed General , told him:- Alfonso , if it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King , it must be denied urgently and I want to know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing|conj\this interlocutor , who was none other than the Armed General , told him:- Alfonso , if it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King , it must be denied urgently and I want to know urgently – and the King almost shouted – why Tejero said such a thing|conj\thim:-|dobj\tif it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King|advcl\tthat this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King|ccomp\tin the name of the King|prep\tAlfonso , if it is true that this madman has entered the Congress in the name of the King , it must be denied urgently|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.5101,
                    "answers": "than the Armed General|prep\tthe Armed General|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- And just hung up the phone.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened to the phone on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "just hung up the phone"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com do to hang up the phone?",
                    "score": 0.7512,
                    "answers": "that - And just hung up the phone|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the person who hung up the phone?",
                    "score": 0.7034,
                    "answers": "the phone|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5994,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5866,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - And just hung up the phone|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tAnd|cc\tjust|advmod\tup|prt\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I approached and without sitting, standing (there sitting the Queen followed).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I approached and without sitting?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did the Queen sit in a sitting position?",
                    "score": 0.7952,
                    "answers": "( there sitting the Queen followed )|parataxis"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take for the Queen to sit in a chair?",
                    "score": 0.7832,
                    "answers": "there sitting|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the first Queen to meet with the Queen?",
                    "score": 0.7271,
                    "answers": "the Queen|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "When did the Queen meet with Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.7129,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sitting and sitting?",
                    "score": 0.5666,
                    "answers": "without sitting , standing|conj\tsitting ,|acl\tsitting , standing|pcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Sir, I see you already know.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about the claim?",
                    "score": 0.7555,
                    "answers": "that - Sir , I see you already know|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6147,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6044,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Sir , I see you already know|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tSir|npadvmod\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tyou|nsubj\talready|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the link between the letter from the Mediterraneodigital.com and the website?",
                    "score": 0.5859,
                    "answers": "you already know|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Yes, Sabino, the thing is serious.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Yes, Sabino, the thing serious?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's stance on abortion?",
                    "score": 0.7773,
                    "answers": "that - Yes , Sabino , the thing is serious|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's position on abortion?",
                    "score": 0.7591,
                    "answers": "the thing|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Sabino's involvement in the drug trade?",
                    "score": 0.7591,
                    "answers": "the|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sabino and socialism?",
                    "score": 0.6696,
                    "answers": "Yes|intj\tserious|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6138,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I think we should authorize the Navy to come to the Zarzuela and explain in detail what's going on, because I think things are happening here that weren't planned.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that we should authorize the Navy to come to the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did the Navy come to Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.8566,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I think we should authorize the Navy to come to the Zarzuela and explain in detail what 's going on , because I think things are happening here that were n't planned|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about the Navy joining the Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.7402,
                    "answers": "should|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of allowing the Navy to come to Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.7011,
                    "answers": "we should authorize the Navy to come to the Zarzuela and explain in detail what 's going on , because I think things are happening here that were n't planned|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the Navy coming to Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.684,
                    "answers": "because I think things are happening here that were n't planned|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Navy and the Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.6457,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthe|det\tthe Navy|dobj\tthe|det\tin detail|prep\t's|aux\tthings|nsubj\tare|aux\tthings are happening here that were n't planned|ccomp\there|advmod\twere|auxpass\tn't|neg"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Things that were not foreseen?What does Your Majesty mean?- Well, it is a saying (but, for the first time I noticed a certain nervousness in the King, as if he wanted to hide something from me)- Well, sir, I still think that the Armed General should stay in his post.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Things that were not foreseen?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the king have for the first time that made him feel like he wanted to hide something from me?",
                    "answer": "nervousness"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who should stay in his post?",
                    "answer": "the Armed General"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of the phrase \" Things that were not foreseen?",
                    "score": 0.6016,
                    "answers": "that were not foreseen?What|relcl\tYour Majesty|nsubj\tdoes Your Majesty mean?-|ROOT\tit|nsubj\ta|det\tbut|cc\tfor the first time|prep\tthe|det\tthe first time|pobj\ta|det\tthe|det\tto hide something from me)-|xcomp\tsomething|dobj\tfrom me)-|prep\tme)-|pobj\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.5551,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj\twww.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Things that were not foreseen?What|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the King and the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.5356,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tYour|poss\tWell , it is a saying ( but , for the first time I noticed a certain nervousness in the King , as if he wanted to hide something from me)-|ROOT\tI|nsubj\t, for the first time I noticed a certain nervousness in the King , as if he wanted to hide something from me)-|conj\tcertain|amod\ta certain nervousness in the King ,|dobj\tin the King|prep\tthe King|pobj\the|nsubj\tI|nsubj\tstill|advmod\tin his post|prep\this|poss\this post|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Sir, I think it's urgent that Your Majesty speak directly to the Captains General to know what they think and what's going on in their respective regions.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who should speak directly to the Captains General?",
                    "answer": "Your Majesty"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the importance of speaking directly to the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.6558,
                    "answers": "it 's urgent that Your Majesty speak directly to the Captains General to know what they think and what 's going on in their respective regions|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.6507,
                    "answers": "to the Captains General|prep\tCaptains|compound\tthe Captains General|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the quotes from the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.6453,
                    "answers": "'s|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Captains General and the British Prime Minister?",
                    "score": 0.6248,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tit|nsubj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthey|nsubj\tand|cc\ton|prt\ttheir|poss\trespective|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5408,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I also think it's urgent that His Majesty publicly disprove what Tejero is saying in Congress.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who should disprove what Tejero is saying in Congress?",
                    "answer": "His Majesty"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Tejero say in Congress?",
                    "score": 0.8506,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I also think it 's urgent that His Majesty publicly disprove what Tejero is saying in Congress|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\talso|advmod\tthat I also think it 's urgent that His Majesty publicly disprove what Tejero is saying in Congress|ccomp\tit|nsubj\tit 's urgent that His Majesty publicly disprove what Tejero is saying in Congress|ccomp\turgent|acomp\tthat|mark\tHis|poss\tHis Majesty|nsubj\tpublicly|advmod\tthat His Majesty publicly disprove what Tejero is saying in Congress|ccomp\twhat|dobj\tis|aux\twhat Tejero is saying in Congress|ccomp\tin Congress|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5848,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I think it should be addressed to the Spanish on Spanish Television.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I think it should be addressed to the Spanish on Spanish Television?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5999,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.588,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I think it should be addressed to the Spanish on Spanish Television|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tthat I think it should be addressed to the Spanish on Spanish Television|ccomp\tit|nsubjpass\tshould|aux\tbe|auxpass\tit should be addressed to the Spanish on Spanish Television|ccomp\tto the Spanish|prep\tthe|det\ton Spanish Television|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Menditerraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.514,
                    "answers": "the Spanish|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- All right, you make the arrangements with TV and as soon as you're done you come here and talk to the Captains General.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - All right, you make the arrangements with TV and then come here and talk to the Captains General?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say to the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.6758,
                    "answers": "you|nsubj\tTV|pobj\tyou|nsubjpass\t're|auxpass\tyou|nsubj\tas soon as you 're done you come here and talk to the Captains General|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.6638,
                    "answers": "talk to the Captains General|conj\tto the Captains General|prep\tthe Captains General|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between TV and the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.6015,
                    "answers": "the arrangements|dobj\twith TV|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5554,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5342,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t-|punct\tAll|advmod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tand|cc\tas|advmod\tas|mark\there|advmod\tand|cc\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "So I went back to my office, where Fernando Gutierrez was supernervous, who without wasting time told me:- Sabino, the military have taken Spanish Television and National Radio.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Fernando Gutierrez tell me?",
                    "answer": "Sabino, the military have taken Spanish Television and National Radio"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Sabino say to Gutierrez about his involvement in the government?",
                    "score": 0.741,
                    "answers": "without wasting time|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Sabino and Gutierrez?",
                    "score": 0.6136,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tSo|advmod\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Gutierrez being supernervous?",
                    "score": 0.5933,
                    "answers": "supernervous|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's role in the military?",
                    "score": 0.5913,
                    "answers": "the military|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Gutierrez and Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.5794,
                    "answers": "Fernando|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- What do you say? - I've just been confirmed by the Director General himself.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who confirmed that I've been confirmed by Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "answer": "the Director General"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who confirmed the Director General?",
                    "score": 0.8565,
                    "answers": "by the Director General himself|agent"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Director General in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7832,
                    "answers": "the Director General himself|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Director General and Barack Obama?",
                    "score": 0.768,
                    "answers": "that - What do you say ? - I 've just been confirmed by the Director General himself|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Director General?",
                    "score": 0.7515,
                    "answers": "What|dobj\tdo|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the director general of Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6871,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tDirector|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "At the time the phone rang.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that the phone rang?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the phone ring on 23/02/2018?",
                    "score": 0.7907,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the time of the phone ring?",
                    "score": 0.74,
                    "answers": "the time|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5677,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that At the time the phone rang|ROOT\tthat|mark\tAt the time|prep\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe phone|nsubj\tthat At the time the phone rang|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It was General Juste asking to talk to me.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who asked to talk to me on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "General Juste"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did General Juste ask to talk to?",
                    "score": 0.8389,
                    "answers": "that It was General Juste asking to talk to me|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was General Juste asked to talk to?",
                    "score": 0.8008,
                    "answers": "me|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of General Juste asking to talk to me?",
                    "score": 0.7173,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that It was General Juste asking to talk to me|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tGeneral|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is General Juste?",
                    "score": 0.705,
                    "answers": "General Juste|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6396,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I quickly got in touch.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I quickly got in touch with them?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.7363,
                    "answers": "that I quickly got in touch|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.61,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.572,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I quickly got in touch|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tquickly|advmod\tin touch|prep\ttouch|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Juste, what's going on? - Sabino (General Juste and I were very close since my stay at the Army Ministry).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Juste, what was going on?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the general who was close to Juste since his stay at the Army Ministry?",
                    "answer": "Sabino"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Sabino and Juste?",
                    "score": 0.6389,
                    "answers": "what - Sabino|nsubj\t- Sabino|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Juste and Juste?",
                    "score": 0.5999,
                    "answers": "General Juste and I|nsubj\t( General Juste and I were very close since my stay at the Army Ministry )|parataxis\tsince my stay at the Army Ministry|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5172,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Is the Armed General in the Zarzuela?- No, why do you ask me?- Because I have been told that at this time the Armed General had to be in the Zarzuela.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that the Armed General was in the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "No, why do you ask me?-"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is in the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "the Armed General"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is the armed general in Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.7079,
                    "answers": "to be in the Zarzuela|xcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- And why is that?Who has informed you of it?- Commander Pardo Zancada, who apparently knows from the mouth of General Milans.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did Commander Pardo Zancada know from the mouth of?",
                    "answer": "General Milans"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did Commander Pardo Zancada know from the mouth of?",
                    "answer": "General Milans"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Pardo Zancada know from the mouth of General Milans?",
                    "score": 0.7866,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - And why is that?Who has informed you of it?- Commander Pardo Zancada , who apparently knows from the mouth of General Milans|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tAnd|cc\twhy|advmod\tthat - And why is|ccomp\tthat?Who|punct\thas|aux\thas informed you of it?-|ccomp\tyou|dobj\tof|prep\tit?-|punct\tCommander|compound\tCommander Pardo Zancada , who apparently knows from the mouth of General Milans|dobj\t,|punct\twho|nsubj\tapparently|advmod\twho apparently knows from the mouth of General Milans|relcl\tfrom the mouth of General Milans|prep\tthe|det\tGeneral|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Pardo Zancada?",
                    "score": 0.6956,
                    "answers": "Pardo|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Well, Juste, Navy isn't in the Zarzuela, neither is it nor is it expected.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that Juste, Navy isn't in the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What branch of the military isn't in the Zarzuela?",
                    "answer": "Navy"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Juste say about the Navy being in Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.83,
                    "answers": "is it nor is it expected|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is the Zarzuela located?",
                    "score": 0.8219,
                    "answers": "in the Zarzuela|prep\tthe Zarzuela|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is the Navy located in Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.8186,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat - Well , Juste , Navy is n't in the Zarzuela , neither is it nor is it expected|parataxis"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the Navy in Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.7662,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Well , Juste , Navy is n't in the Zarzuela , neither is it nor is it expected|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Navy and Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.7368,
                    "answers": "is it expected|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Thank you, Sabino, that changes things.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Thank you, Sabino, that changed things?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's position on abortion?",
                    "score": 0.7716,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sabino and Obama?",
                    "score": 0.7211,
                    "answers": "that - Thank you , Sabino , that changes things|parataxis"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's track record with the government?",
                    "score": 0.7115,
                    "answers": "-|punct\tyou|dobj\t,|punct\t,|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Thanks again.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com say on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "Thanks again"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5784,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5569,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Thanks again|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tthat Thanks again|ccomp\tagain|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Hey, hey, why do things change?What things?- Sabino, please, I'll call you later.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Hey, hey, why do things change?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "Hey, hey, why do things change?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "Sabino, please, I'll call you later"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Sabino's claims?",
                    "score": 0.6743,
                    "answers": "things?-|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.6709,
                    "answers": "you|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sabino and Trump?",
                    "score": 0.6708,
                    "answers": "do|aux\tplease|intj\tI|nsubj\tlater|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.611,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.577,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Hey , hey , why do things change?What things?-|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I hung up the phone and my head was a boil.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened to my head when I hung up the phone?",
                    "answer": "a boil"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the cause of the boil on the phone?",
                    "score": 0.7004,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I hung up the phone and my head was a boil|ROOT\tthat I hung up the phone and my head was a boil|ccomp\tmy head was a boil|conj\ta boil|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the person who hung up the phone?",
                    "score": 0.6266,
                    "answers": "up|prt\tmy head|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5994,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5708,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe phone|dobj\tand|cc\tmy|poss\ta|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For the first time I sensed something about the Armed General, perhaps because of his insistence on going to the Zarzuela.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that for the first time I sensed something about the Armed General?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did the armed general want to go to Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.861,
                    "answers": "perhaps because of his insistence on going to the Zarzuela|prep\this insistence on going to the Zarzuela|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of the armed general?",
                    "score": 0.6547,
                    "answers": "something about the Armed General|dobj\tabout the Armed General|prep\tArmed|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the armed general and Zarzuela?",
                    "score": 0.5814,
                    "answers": "that For the first time I sensed something about the Armed General , perhaps because of his insistence on going to the Zarzuela|ccomp\tthe Zarzuela|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.557,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "My instinct has already put me on guard.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What has already put me on guard?",
                    "answer": "My instinct"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What has My instinct put me on guard?",
                    "score": 0.845,
                    "answers": "on guard|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is My instinct?",
                    "score": 0.7687,
                    "answers": "My instinct|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between guard and guard?",
                    "score": 0.6878,
                    "answers": "guard|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6143,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that My instinct has already put me on guard|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tMy|poss\thas|aux\talready|advmod\tthat My instinct has already put me on guard|ccomp\tme|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6135,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Also that the news of the Navy would have arrived through Milans del Bosch.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did the news of the Navy come from?",
                    "answer": "Milans del Bosch"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did the news of the Navy arrive at Milans del Bosch?",
                    "score": 0.7729,
                    "answers": "that Also that the news of the Navy would have arrived through Milans del Bosch|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Navy say about Milans del Bosch?",
                    "score": 0.7345,
                    "answers": "of the Navy|prep\tthe Navy|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the location of Milans del Bosch?",
                    "score": 0.6821,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tdel|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Milans del Bosch?",
                    "score": 0.6467,
                    "answers": "through Milans del Bosch|prep\tMilans|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And so, already with 'all the flies behind my ear ', I went back to His Majesty's office and when I entered I took the surprise of the night, what I say, the surprise of my life.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the bug that caused me to go back to His Majesty's office?",
                    "answer": "'all the flies behind my ear"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the bug that caused me to go back to His Majesty's office?",
                    "answer": "'all the flies behind my ear"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of visiting the Her Majesty's office?",
                    "score": 0.6373,
                    "answers": "back to His Majesty 's office|advmod\tto His Majesty 's office|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the significance of the visit to His Majesty's office?",
                    "score": 0.6373,
                    "answers": "the surprise of my life|appos\tof my life|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the fly that visited His Majesty's office?",
                    "score": 0.616,
                    "answers": "that And so , already with ' all the flies behind my ear ' , I went back to His Majesty 's office and when I entered I took the surprise of the night , what I say , the surprise of my life|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5328,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And that clouded my mind and enraged me.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that And that clouded my mind and enraged me?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did this report do for me?",
                    "answer": "clouded my mind"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about it?",
                    "score": 0.6776,
                    "answers": "that And that clouded my mind and enraged me|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the quotes from Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5719,
                    "answers": "my mind|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5584,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.553,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that And that clouded my mind and enraged me|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tAnd|cc\tthat|nsubj\tmy|poss\tand|cc\tme|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "So, and without protocols, I turned to His Majesty and without thinking, I said to him, looking straight at him: - Sir!.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I turned to His Majesty?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What protocols does Mediterraneodigital.com follow?",
                    "score": 0.7734,
                    "answers": "protocols|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between the British Prime Minister and the Russian Prime Minister?",
                    "score": 0.7145,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tSo|advmod\t,|punct\tand|cc\t,|punct\tHis|poss\tand|cc\t,|punct\t,|punct\tstraight|advmod\t-|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the person who was looking straight at him?",
                    "score": 0.6252,
                    "answers": "him|pobj\thim|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6186,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Are you crazy?We're on the edge of the cliff and you're toasting with champagne – and I almost screamed – Sir!Don't you realize that the Monarchy is in danger?Don't you realize that it can be the end of your Reign?Remember what happened to your grandfather!!!Then the King's face changed color and I saw how his hands began to tremble and in an almost inaudible voice he sent out to those present, who immediately left the office.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did you realize about the Monarchy?",
                    "answer": "Monarchy is in danger?Don't you realize that it can be the end of your Reign?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What kind of voice did the King have?",
                    "answer": "inaudible"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How did the King's hands tremble?",
                    "score": 0.7434,
                    "answers": "how his hands began to tremble|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the King say about the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.7133,
                    "answers": "that it can be the end of your Reign?Remember|ccomp\tthe end of your Reign?Remember|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did the King send a message to?",
                    "score": 0.6889,
                    "answers": "those present , who immediately left the office|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that claims that the Monarchy is in danger?",
                    "score": 0.645,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Are you crazy?We're on the edge of the cliff and you 're toasting with champagne – and I almost screamed –|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the King and the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.6212,
                    "answers": "crazy?We're on the edge of the cliff and you 're toasting with champagne – and I almost screamed –|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "(*) All but the Queen, who had a poker face.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that all except the Queen had a poker face?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did the Queen have a poker face?",
                    "score": 0.8833,
                    "answers": "that ( * ) All but the Queen , who had a poker face|ccomp\tbut the Queen , who had a poker face|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of the Queen having a poker face?",
                    "score": 0.829,
                    "answers": "who had a poker face|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the poker face that the Queen had?",
                    "score": 0.8006,
                    "answers": "poker|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6779,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Queen and Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6663,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\twho|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Once alone His Majesty came to me, and trembling and almost crying, he took me by the hands and in a supplicant tone he said to me: - Sabino, please save me! Save me, save the Monarchy, right now I do not know what I do or what to say! - Majesty, let us all calm down.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "In what tone did His Majesty say to me?",
                    "answer": "supplicant"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did His Majesty say to Sabino?",
                    "answer": "Save me, save the Monarchy,"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did His Majesty say to us?",
                    "answer": "calm down"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How did Sabino save his Majesty?",
                    "score": 0.671,
                    "answers": "trembling and almost crying , he took me by the hands and in a supplicant tone he said to me : - Sabino , please save me !|conj\tin a supplicant tone he said to me : - Sabino , please save me !|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who saved the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.6273,
                    "answers": "His|poss\tme|pobj\the|nsubj\tme|dobj\tthe|det\tin a supplicant tone|prep\the|nsubj\tme|pobj\tme|dobj\tme|dobj\tsave the Monarchy|advcl\tthe|det\tSave me , save the Monarchy , right now I do not know what I do or what to say !|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Sabino say to his Majesty in a supplicant tone?",
                    "score": 0.6106,
                    "answers": "His Majesty|nsubj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tand|cc\t,|punct\tand|cc\tsupplicant|amod\t:|punct\t-|punct\t,|punct\tplease|intj\t!|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tnot|neg\twhat|dobj\tI|nsubj\tor|cc\twhat|dobj\t!|punct\t-|punct\tMajesty|npadvmod\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Sabino do to save the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.5881,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthe hands|pobj\tSabino , please save me|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the supplicant tone of the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.5566,
                    "answers": "a supplicant tone|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This is not the time for sorrows.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that This is not the time for sorrows?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of the term \" sorrows\"?",
                    "score": 0.7559,
                    "answers": "sorrows|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about sorrows?",
                    "score": 0.7401,
                    "answers": "that This is not the time for sorrows|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the time for sorrows?",
                    "score": 0.7179,
                    "answers": "the time for sorrows|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6075,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that This is not the time for sorrows|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tThis|nsubj\tnot|neg\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "You yourself told me before that we should not lose our calm in difficult times.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that You yourself told me before that we should not lose our calm in difficult times?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about our calm in difficult times?",
                    "score": 0.7423,
                    "answers": "that we should not lose our calm in difficult times|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6264,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj\tin difficult times|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5795,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that You yourself told me before that we should not lose our calm in difficult times|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tYou yourself|nsubj\tyourself|appos\tme|dobj\tbefore|advmod\tthat|mark\twe|nsubj\tshould|aux\tnot|neg\tour|poss\tdifficult|amod\tdifficult times|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.572,
                    "answers": "our calm|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "What needs to be done is to try to control the situation and to do this it is essential to talk to the Captains General.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is one thing that needs to be done?",
                    "answer": "to try to control the situation"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the Captains General do to control the situation?",
                    "score": 0.8003,
                    "answers": "to control the situation|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to talk to the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.7957,
                    "answers": "to do this it is essential to talk to the Captains General|conj\tto talk to the Captains General|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What needs to be done to control the situation of the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.7794,
                    "answers": "What needs to be done|csubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.7039,
                    "answers": "the|det\tto the Captains General|prep\tthe|det\tCaptains|compound\tthe Captains General|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5769,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I warn you that Brunete has already taken Spanish Television and National Radio.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "that Brunete has already taken Spanish Television and National Radio"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Brunete taking Spanish Television and National Radio?",
                    "score": 0.7539,
                    "answers": "Spanish|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Brunete and National Radio?",
                    "score": 0.7016,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I warn you that Brunete has already taken Spanish Television and National Radio|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tthat I warn you that Brunete has already taken Spanish Television and National Radio|ccomp\tyou|dobj\tthat|mark\thas|aux\talready|advmod\tthat Brunete has already taken Spanish Television and National Radio|ccomp\tSpanish Television and National Radio|dobj\tand|cc\tNational|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6227,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I knew it, I knew it! - What did you know, Lord?- What was going to happenAt that moment the Queen got up and without saying anything left the office.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I knew it, I knew it?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Queen do when she left the office?",
                    "answer": "What was going to happenAt that moment the Queen got up and without saying anything left the office"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the Queen get up and leave the office?",
                    "score": 0.7861,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I knew it , I knew it !|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tI knew it|ccomp\tit|dobj\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tthat I knew it , I knew it|ccomp\tit|dobj\t!|punct\t-|punct\tWhat|dobj\t,|punct\tWhat|nsubj\twas|aux\t- What did you know , Lord?- What was going to happenAt that moment the Queen got up and without saying anything left the office|ROOT\tto|aux\tthat|det\tthe|det\tthe Queen|nsubj\tthe Queen got up and without saying anything left the office|ccomp\tup|prt\tand|cc\twithout saying anything|prep\twithout saying anything left the office|conj\tthe|det\tthe office|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Queen say to the media after she got up?",
                    "score": 0.7602,
                    "answers": "saying anything|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Elizabeth and the Lord?",
                    "score": 0.6939,
                    "answers": "did|aux\tanything|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5517,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.531,
                    "answers": "you|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "My legs were shaking.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was shaking on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "My legs"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of shaking?",
                    "score": 0.8462,
                    "answers": "My|poss\tthat My legs were shaking|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.?",
                    "score": 0.6479,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that My legs were shaking|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6308,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6015,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\twere|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Then the King sat at his table and laid his head in his hands.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that Then the King sat at his table and laid his head in his hands?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the King lay his head in his hands?",
                    "score": 0.7699,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat Then the King sat at his table and laid his head in his hands|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5543,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I sat across the street and waited a few seconds before talking.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take for me to talk to someone?",
                    "answer": "waited a few seconds"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to wait for a speech to be completed?",
                    "score": 0.7536,
                    "answers": "before talking|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did Mediterraneodigital.com wait to talk?",
                    "score": 0.6805,
                    "answers": "that I sat across the street and waited a few seconds before talking|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5894,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5687,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I sat across the street and waited a few seconds before talking|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tacross the street|prep\tthe|det\tthe street|pobj\tand|cc\ta|det\tfew|amod\ttalking|pcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Sir, I don't know what Your Majesty knew, but whatever it is, now what you have to do is stop this madness.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "stop this madness"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say?",
                    "score": 0.7966,
                    "answers": "you have what to do|csubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.7923,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\tdo|aux\tn't|neg\twhat|dobj\tYour|poss\t,|punct\tbut|cc\twhatever|attr\tit|nsubj\t,|punct\tnow|advmod\twhat|dobj\tyou|nsubj\tto|aux\twhat to do|xcomp\tthis|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the method used to stop the madness?",
                    "score": 0.7531,
                    "answers": "whatever it is , now you have what to do is stop this madness|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the quotes from the Queen?",
                    "score": 0.6991,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Sir , I do n't know what Your Majesty knew , but whatever it is , now you have what to do is stop this madness|ROOT\tSir|npadvmod\twhatever it is|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the mediterraneodigital website?",
                    "score": 0.6778,
                    "answers": "stop this madness|xcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If it succeeds, the Monarchy will fall like his grandfather's.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What will fall like his grandfather's?",
                    "answer": "the Monarchy"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What will happen if the monarchy is successful?",
                    "score": 0.8642,
                    "answers": "that If it succeeds , the Monarchy will fall like his grandfather 's|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.7076,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Please talk to the Captains General and do what you can.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that you should talk to?",
                    "answer": "Captains General"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.7748,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Please talk to the Captains General and do what you can|ROOT\tto the Captains General|prep\tCaptains|compound\tthe Captains General|pobj\tyou|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say to the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.7632,
                    "answers": "do what you can|conj\twhat you can|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6637,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.636,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tPlease|intj\tthe|det\tand|cc\tcan|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Captains General and Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6187,
                    "answers": "that Please talk to the Captains General and do what you can|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- No, sir, with the Captains General, the Supreme Chief of the Armed Forces has to speak, and that honor belongs to His Majesty.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Supreme Chief of the Armed Forces?",
                    "answer": "His Majesty"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What position does the Captains General hold?",
                    "score": 0.868,
                    "answers": "with the Captains General|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Captains General?",
                    "score": 0.7415,
                    "answers": "the Captains General|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Supreme Chief of the Armed Forces?",
                    "score": 0.6948,
                    "answers": "the Supreme Chief of the Armed Forces|nsubj\tof the Armed Forces|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5611,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And there I remained while the King spoke by this order, with Jaime Milans del Bosch (III Military Region), Guillermo Quintana Lacacci (I Region), Pedro Merry Gordon (II Region), Antonio Pascual Galmes (IV Region), Antonio Elícegui Prieto (V Region), Luis Polanco Mejorada (VI Region), Angel Capano Lopez (VII Region), Manuel Fernández Posse (VIII Region), Antonio Delgado Álvarez (IX Region), Manuel de la Torre Pascual (Baleares), Jesús González de Yerro (Canarias) and Ignacio Alfaro Arregui, at that time Chairman of the Board of Chiefs of Staff (JUJEM) and Luis Arebalo Peyuz, admiral head of the General Staff of the Navy.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that And there I remained while the King spoke by this order?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What position did Luis Arebalo Peyuz hold in the General Staff of the Navy?",
                    "score": 0.697,
                    "answers": "at that time Chairman of the Board of Chiefs of Staff ( JUJEM ) and Luis Arebalo Peyuz , admiral head of the General Staff of the Navy|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was Luis Polanco Mejorada's rank in the Navy?",
                    "score": 0.6899,
                    "answers": "admiral|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What region did Antonio Pascual Galmes represent?",
                    "score": 0.6861,
                    "answers": "IV|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of Luis Polanco Mejorada's region?",
                    "score": 0.6726,
                    "answers": "Manuel|compound\tFernández|compound\tManuel|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the chairman of the Board of Chiefs of Staff (JUJEM)?",
                    "score": 0.6641,
                    "answers": "of the Board of Chiefs of Staff ( JUJEM )|prep\tthe Board of Chiefs of Staff ( JUJEM )|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "What the King talked about with the senior army commanders I will talk about in the next installment'.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the King talk about with senior army commanders in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7721,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthe King talked What about with the senior army commanders|pobj\tarmy|compound\tthat I will talk the King talked What about with the senior army commanders about in the next installment|ccomp\tthe King talked What about with the senior army commanders about|prep\tin the next installment|prep\tthe next installment|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who are the senior army commanders?",
                    "score": 0.7326,
                    "answers": "the senior army commanders|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the King and senior army commanders?",
                    "score": 0.7069,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tWhat|pobj\tthe|det\tthe King|nsubj\tWhat about|prep\twith the senior army commanders|prep\tthe|det\tsenior|amod\tI|nsubj\twill|aux\tthe|det\tnext|amod\t'|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- This is a bomb, Sabino! - I know.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - This is a bomb, Sabino!",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the website say about Sabino?",
                    "answer": "I know"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of bomb is Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.8371,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - This is a bomb , Sabino ! - I know|ROOT\tThis is a bomb , Sabino !|meta\ta bomb|attr\tthat - This is a bomb , Sabino ! - I know|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.7109,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tThis|nsubj\ta|det\t,|punct\t!|punct\t-|punct\tI|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Sabino?",
                    "score": 0.7084,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- This changes history.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - This changes history?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of history?",
                    "score": 0.722,
                    "answers": "history|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5677,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - This changes history|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tThis|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But it's the truth.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that But it's the truth?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "it's the truth"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the truth?",
                    "score": 0.7042,
                    "answers": "the truth|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6506,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the truth of Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.65,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that But it 's the truth|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tBut|cc\tthat But it 's the truth|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6376,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tit|nsubj\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Will your 'Memories 'be? - No, you know I'm not in favor of 'Memories'.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the document that was reported on 23/02/2018 by www.mediterraneodigital.com that said 'No, you know I'm not in favor of?",
                    "answer": "'Memories"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com say about 'Memories'?",
                    "answer": "No, you know I'm not in favor"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about memory?",
                    "score": 0.8262,
                    "answers": "- No , you know I 'm not in favor of ' Memories '|parataxis\tI 'm not in favor of ' Memories '|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between memory and memory?",
                    "score": 0.8056,
                    "answers": "of ' Memories '|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.7064,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6848,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - Will your ' Memories ' be ? - No , you know I 'm not in favor of ' Memories '|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Memories are a very serious and very detailed thing.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a very serious and very detailed thing?",
                    "answer": "Memories"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about memory?",
                    "score": 0.8029,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tMemories|nsubj\ta|det\tvery|advmod\tvery serious and very detailed|amod\tand|cc\tvery|advmod\ta very serious and very detailed thing|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between memory and memory?",
                    "score": 0.7703,
                    "answers": "that Memories are a very serious and very detailed thing|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.7471,
                    "answers": "very detailed|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5997,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5825,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Memories are a very serious and very detailed thing|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- But, I understand this is just the beginning of what happened that evening-night.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did they say about what happened on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "I understand this is just the beginning"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the beginning of the evening-night program?",
                    "score": 0.6404,
                    "answers": "that - But , I understand this is just the beginning of what happened that evening - night|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the evidence of what happened during the evening-night time?",
                    "score": 0.6226,
                    "answers": "of what happened that evening - night|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the evening-night event?",
                    "score": 0.6104,
                    "answers": "But|cc\tthis|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that is linked to the evening-night event?",
                    "score": 0.6071,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the origin of the evening-night story?",
                    "score": 0.5993,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - But , I understand this is just the beginning of what happened that evening - night|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- That's right, next Saturday I'll show you what I write these days, if I feel like it, because I have my doubts.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what day will I show you what I write?",
                    "answer": "Saturday"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about writing?",
                    "score": 0.826,
                    "answers": "next|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of who wrote these days?",
                    "score": 0.6539,
                    "answers": "what I write these days|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5902,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5564,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that - That 's right , next Saturday I 'll show you what I write these days , if I feel like it , because I have my doubts|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\t-|punct\tThat|nsubj\tright|acomp\t,|punct\tI|nsubj\t'll|aux\tyou|dobj\twhat|dobj\tI|nsubj\tthese|det\t,|punct\tif|mark\tI|nsubj\tif I feel like it|advcl\tlike it|prep\tit|pobj\t,|punct\tbecause|mark\tI|nsubj\tmy|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Sometimes I think that the history that has been written of'that 'is already immovable.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "that"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the history that has been written of'that?",
                    "score": 0.6672,
                    "answers": "the history that has been written of'that '|nsubj\tof'that '|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5763,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5387,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Sometimes I think that the history that has been written of'that ' is already immovable|ROOT\tthat|mark\tSometimes|advmod\tI|nsubj\tthat|mark\tthat|nsubjpass\tbeen|auxpass\t'|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Besides, I'm looking like the Prometheus in chains.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the Greek god in chains?",
                    "answer": "the Prometheus"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.7925,
                    "answers": "I|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about the Prometheus in chains?",
                    "score": 0.7705,
                    "answers": "Besides|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com look like?",
                    "score": 0.7439,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t,|punct\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6334,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Yeah, I'm chained to my own words and everything I've been saying since 1981.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Yeah, I'm chained to my own words and everything I've been saying since 1981?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are I chained to?",
                    "answer": "my own words"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What words has Barack Obama been saying since 1981?",
                    "score": 0.7841,
                    "answers": "own|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What words have been linked to Barack Obama since 1981?",
                    "score": 0.7394,
                    "answers": "my own words and everything I 've been saying since 1981|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long has Mediterraneodigital.com been running?",
                    "score": 0.6577,
                    "answers": "I 've been saying since 1981|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between words and speech?",
                    "score": 0.6263,
                    "answers": "that - Yeah , I 'm chained to my own words and everything I 've been saying since 1981|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the quotes from Barack Obama about his own words and everything he said since 1981?",
                    "score": 0.5961,
                    "answers": "'ve|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I helped create the version that has passed to history and now I'm sure they'd all face it.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that I helped create the version that passed to history?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who created the version that passed to history?",
                    "score": 0.8393,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat I helped create the version that has passed to history and now I 'm sure they 'd all face it|ccomp\tcreate the version that has passed to history|xcomp\tthe version that has passed to history|dobj\tthat has passed to history|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who helped create the version that has passed to history?",
                    "score": 0.8386,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I helped create the version that has passed to history and now I 'm sure they 'd all face it|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6092,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5828,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tthat|nsubj\tand|cc\tnow|advmod\tthey|nsubj\tall|dep\tit|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Many would blame me for speaking now with resentment, for the'kick in the ass'that His Majesty gave me last year.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who gave me a kick in the ass?",
                    "answer": "His Majesty"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about Trump's relationship with His Majesty?",
                    "score": 0.7242,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tHis|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com do?",
                    "score": 0.6275,
                    "answers": "now|advmod\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Elizabeth and Her Majesty?",
                    "score": 0.6253,
                    "answers": "His Majesty|nsubj\tHis Majesty gave me last year|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between Mezvinsky and His Majesty?",
                    "score": 0.5568,
                    "answers": "me|dobj\twith resentment|prep\tresentment|pobj\tthe ass'that|pobj\tme|dobj\tlast|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5384,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- No, Sabino, your prestige as a serious man is beyond doubt and I'm sure they'll believe you at their feet.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where will they believe you?",
                    "answer": "at their feet"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's political affiliation?",
                    "score": 0.7103,
                    "answers": "beyond doubt|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sabino's prestige as a serious man?",
                    "score": 0.7092,
                    "answers": "I 'm sure they 'll believe you at their feet|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website Sabino is a serious man?",
                    "score": 0.686,
                    "answers": "-|punct\tNo|intj\tand|cc\tI|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sabino and a serious man?",
                    "score": 0.6755,
                    "answers": "your|poss\ta|det\tserious|amod\tyou|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Many events in history have suffered significant changes and changes over time.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.mediterraneodigital.com report on 23/02/2018",
                    "answer": "Many events in history have suffered significant changes and changes over time"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many events in history have suffered significant changes and changes over time?",
                    "score": 0.8027,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tin history|prep\thistory|pobj\thave|aux\tchanges|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.577,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5416,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tMany|amod\tsignificant|amod\tand|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "What I'm concerned about is the position the Monarch can take if your version of now becomes public.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is concerned about what if your version of now becomes public?",
                    "answer": "the Monarch"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What position does the Monarch hold?",
                    "score": 0.8727,
                    "answers": "What I 'm|auxpass\tthe Monarch|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What position can the Monarch take if it becomes public?",
                    "score": 0.8393,
                    "answers": "the position the Monarch can take if your version of now becomes public|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Dr. George Flinn's position on the Monarch?",
                    "score": 0.7403,
                    "answers": "that What I 'm concerned about|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Monarch and the republicans?",
                    "score": 0.7236,
                    "answers": "your version of now|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6234,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- It could be until the fall of the Monarchy.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the website say could be before the end of the Monarchy?",
                    "answer": "the fall of the Monarchy"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long could it be until the fall of the monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.8738,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t-|punct\tIt|nsubj\tcould|aux\tthe|det\tof the Monarchy|prep\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.7718,
                    "answers": "the Monarchy|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6798,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Although many do not believe it Spain has no other way out right now than the Monarchy.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that although many do not believe it, Spain has no other way out right now than the Monarchy?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Spain's relationship with the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.8159,
                    "answers": "no other way out right now than the Monarchy|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.7753,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Although many do not believe it Spain has no other way out right now than the Monarchy|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthan the Monarchy|prep\tthe Monarchy|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Spain and the Monarchy?",
                    "score": 0.7647,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tAlthough|mark\tmany|nsubj\tdo|aux\tnot|neg\tAlthough many do not believe it|advcl\tit|dobj\tthat Although many do not believe it Spain has no other way out right now than the Monarchy|ccomp\tno|det\tother|amod\tout|advmod\tright|advmod\tright now|advmod\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.615,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In that maybe Franco was right and everything was tied and well tied!- Yes, but the image of the King'savior of democracy 'will be over.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the image of Franco?",
                    "answer": "the King'savior of democracy"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the image of Franco?",
                    "answer": "the King'savior of democracy"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Franco and the King'savior of democracy?",
                    "score": 0.7062,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that In that maybe Franco was right and everything was tied and well tied!-|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat In that maybe Franco was right and everything was tied and well tied!-|ccomp\teverything|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\teverything was tied and well tied!-|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5014,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Well, that's true, but between History, Monarchy, King or Truth, I prefer to keep the Truth.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that - Well, that's true, but between History, Monarchy, King or Truth, I prefer to keep the Truth?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between History, Monarchy, King or Truth?",
                    "answer": "between History, Monarchy, King or Truth, I prefer to keep the Truth"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Mediterraneodigital.com say about the truth?",
                    "score": 0.7168,
                    "answers": "Truth|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of keeping the truth?",
                    "score": 0.7118,
                    "answers": "to keep the Truth|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between History, Monarchy, and Truth?",
                    "score": 0.7083,
                    "answers": "that - Well , that 's true , but between History , Monarchy , King or Truth , I prefer to keep the Truth|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between History, Monarchy, King or Truth?",
                    "score": 0.7047,
                    "answers": "between History , Monarchy , King or Truth , I prefer to keep the Truth|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the truth?",
                    "score": 0.6955,
                    "answers": "the Truth|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's my conscience.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that it's my conscience?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6301,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.6281,
                    "answers": "my conscience|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5918,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that It 's my conscience|ROOT\ton 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tIt|nsubj\tthat It 's my conscience|ccomp\tmy|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I'm going to turn 77, and I'm already, as Baroja said, on the last bend of the road.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I'm going to turn 77?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When did Baroja turn 77?",
                    "score": 0.8641,
                    "answers": "I 'm already , as Baroja said , on the last bend of the road|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the age limit for turning 77?",
                    "score": 0.7892,
                    "answers": "to turn 77|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long has it been since Baroja turned 77?",
                    "score": 0.7845,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tI|nsubj\tI|nsubj\talready|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long has Baroja been alive?",
                    "score": 0.7577,
                    "answers": ",|punct\tand|cc\t,|punct\tas|mark\tas Baroja said|advcl\t,|punct\tthe|det\tlast|amod\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Baroja say on the last bend of the road?",
                    "score": 0.7238,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that I 'm going to turn 77 , and I 'm already , as Baroja said , on the last bend of the road|ROOT\t'm|aux\tto|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Besides, I owe it to my Lieutenant Rubio, you know the story.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.mediterraneodigital.com report that I owe it to my Lieutenant Rubio?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Rubio say about Lt. Gov. Rubio?",
                    "score": 0.8329,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tBesides|advmod\t,|punct\t,|punct\tyou|nsubj\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Rubio and Lt. Gov. Rubio?",
                    "score": 0.7461,
                    "answers": "I|nsubj\tit|dobj\tmy|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the story of Lt. Gov. Rubio?",
                    "score": 0.7188,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that Besides , I owe it to my Lieutenant Rubio , you know the story|ROOT\tyou know the story|ccomp\tthe story|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Lt. Gov. Rubio?",
                    "score": 0.7106,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat Besides , I owe it to my Lieutenant Rubio , you know the story|ccomp\tto my Lieutenant Rubio|prep\tLieutenant|compound\tmy Lieutenant Rubio|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.6819,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And that's where we left the conversation that day.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/02/2018 that And that's where we left the conversation that day?",
                    "answer": "www.mediterraneodigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What happened on 23/02/2018?",
                    "answer": "that's where we left the conversation"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Mediterraneodigital.com say about the conversation?",
                    "score": 0.6388,
                    "answers": "that And that 's where we left the conversation that day|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the conversation on 23/02/2018?",
                    "score": 0.5518,
                    "answers": "the conversation|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5317,
                    "answers": "on 23/02/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tAnd|cc\tthat|nsubj\twhere|advmod\twe|nsubj\tthe|det\tthat|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "That's when he told me to take the notes I wanted, knowingly, as I had shown him on many occasions that I was a tomb.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did he tell me to take the notes I wanted?",
                    "answer": "23/02/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many times has Dr. George Flinn visited a tomb?",
                    "score": 0.7662,
                    "answers": "on many occasions|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Dr. George Flinn say about being a tomb?",
                    "score": 0.7454,
                    "answers": "that I was a tomb|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many notes did Mediterraneodigital take?",
                    "score": 0.6623,
                    "answers": "when he told me to take the notes I wanted , knowingly , as I had shown him on many occasions that I was a tomb|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the person who told him that he was a tomb?",
                    "score": 0.6252,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com reported on 23/02/2018 that That 's when he told me to take the notes I wanted , knowingly , as I had shown him on many occasions that I was a tomb|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Mediterraneodigital?",
                    "score": 0.5278,
                    "answers": "www.mediterraneodigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}